{
    "id": "bfa74b3d510941cabb369b80c7a88784",
    "title": "Adjective Or Present Participle",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "A rolling stone gathers no moss.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Rolling is an adjective",
                "Rolling is a present participle"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "295e8e78c11f4ac5967e3defa035c995"
        },
        {
            "question": "That was an interesting book.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Interesting is an adjective",
                "Interesting is a present participle"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e54130f0be3748ad95205215fe709617"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are smoking too much.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Smoking is a present participle",
                "Smoking is an adjective"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9d9adbd62aaa456180230afe1e329687"
        },
        {
            "question": "He put the smoking cigarette end in the ashtray.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Smoking is a present participle",
                "Smoking is an adjective"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f387a5c0da964331bd087a66bdff1973"
        },
        {
            "question": "The delay was maddening.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Maddening is an adjective",
                "Maddening is a present participle"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6e2c34e3df5940c9a6f2c5cae03e41f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is waiting for us.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Waiting is an adjective",
                "Waiting is a present participle"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6e07825b458c4866a3eee05605a859d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The scenery was enchanting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Enchanting is an adjective",
                "Enchanting is a present participle"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3955036f50fb4d8586f79de8f3265900"
        },
        {
            "question": "Barking dogs seldom bite.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Barking is an adjective",
                "Barking is a present participle"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3dda760f43544604a7a1478fe3f18c3d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The news was distressing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Distressing is an adjective",
                "Distressing is a present participle"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8052b27bc42e4cc1af9dd06b1a275107"
        },
        {
            "question": "Interesting though it was, I didnâ€™t like the film.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Interesting is an adjective",
                "Interesting is a present participle"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "46397e3d03ba4722acb249f453dcbadd"
        }
    ]
}